b2btrade.biz 2013-09-25

# Privacy Policy of B2btrade.biz - Asia B2B trade Portal for Import Export Business focus on Asia

**Privacy Policy for B2btrade.biz**

Amended & Restated  
Last Updated: 03/04/2009

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers b2btrade.biz's treatment of personally identifiable information that b2btrade.biz collects when you are on the Web site located at www.b2btrade.biz, and when you use b2btrade.biz's services. This policy also covers b2btrade.biz's treatment of any personally identifiable information that b2btrade.biz's business partners share with b2btrade.biz.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that b2btrade.biz does not own or control, or to people that b2btrade.biz does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**

B2Btrade.biz collects personally identifiable information when you register for a b2btrade.biz account and when you use the service. b2btrade.biz may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

When you register with b2btrade.biz, we ask for your email address and some other information. Once you register with b2btrade.biz and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

B2Btrade.biz also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, b2btrade.biz cookie information and the page you requested.

B2Btrade.biz uses your information for the general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see on our pages, and in some cases, to contact you. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

B2Btrade.biz will not provide your personally identifiable information to other companies or people except in the following instances:

* We have your consent to share the information;  
* We need to share your information to provide the service you have requested;  
* We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of b2btrade.biz to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);  
* We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process;  
* We find that your actions on our Web sites violate the b2btrade.biz's Terms of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services; or

**Cookies**

Your Internet browser has a feature called "cookies" which may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. B2Btrade.biz may set and access b2btrade.biz cookies on your computer. However, cookies tell us nothing about who you are unless you specifically give us personally identifiable information.

B2Btrade.biz uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

B2Btrade.biz uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network of web sites and in connection with b2btrade.biz services. 

**DoubleClick DART Cookie:**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Security**

We can't guarantee your email address wont be extracted by a third party email extractor programs. Many of these programs are designed for the purpose of collecting email addresses from search engine and web sites for spaming purposes.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

B2Btrade.biz gives you the ability to edit your b2btrade.biz Account Information and preferences at any time.

You may request deletion of your b2btrade.biz account by sending an email to bizviet@gmail.com. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

B2Btrade.biz may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will notify you by posting a notice on this page of the site. 

**Privacy of Children**

B2Btrade.biz is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age. This requirement is clearly posted during the registration process. 

**Questions or Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback form or send an email to bizviet@gmail.com. 

|    
|   
---  
---  

* * *

About us :: Contact us :: Terms of Use :: Privacy policy :: Advertise with us  
Book Mark this site ! :: Make us your startpage :: Tell a Partner  
**Copyright © 2011 b2btrade.biz.** All rights resevered by
